A Guide to the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia Committee Records, 1964-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Board of Visitors Committee Records
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG 1/1/3.831
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1983 June 30.
Contents List
- Audit Committee Minutes May 1980-May 1983 (Box 1)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes Sep 1982-Jun 1983 (Box 1)
- Educational Policy Committee Minutes Oct 1982-Jun 1983 (Box 1)
- Finance Committee Minutes Sep 1982-Jun 1983 (Box 1)
- Health Affairs Committee Minutes Oct 1982-Jun 1983 (Box 1)
- Student Affairs and Atheletics Committee Minutes Oct 1982-Jun 1983 (Box 1)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Relationship of Alumni Organizations to Board Minutes 1978 Jan-1979 Jan (Box 1)
- Committees (2 folders) 1972 May-1980 Sep (Box 1)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1977-1979 (Box 1)
- Educational Policy Committee Correspondence 1976-1979 (Box 1)
- Executive Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1964-1978 (Box 1)
- Executive Committee Correspondence 1964-1978 (Box 2)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1978-1979 (Box 2)
- Health Affairs Committee Correspondence 1971 Jan-1977 Oct (Box 2)
- Student Affairs and Atheletics Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1969 Nov-1970 Jan 1979 Jan-Oct (Box 2)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Relationship of Alumni Organizations to Board, Correspondence 1978 Jan-1979 Feb (Box 2)
- Special Committee on the Library Correspondence and Minutes 1971 Nov-1973 Apr (Box 2)
- Special Meeting to Hear the Cavalier Daily Appeal 1979 Jan-Mar (Box 2)